{"data":[{"question":"If you ever go into a house in Japan, you must remembering to take off your shoes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"to infer","c":"completely","d":"conclusion","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Conclusion-> conclusions","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"They may nod her head to show that they have understood or shake it to indicate disagreement.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"sanguine","c":"about","d":"successful","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Successful-> success","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The two young woman are watching people dancing, and waiting for an invitation to join in.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"admires","b":"actresses","c":"as","d":"them","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- As-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"When life was simple, man's needs were few and he could supply their all.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"presented","b":"for","c":"of","d":"lost","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Presented-> offered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The train he got on has an accident but he was unharmed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"interested","b":"of","c":"conservation","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Of-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I found it hardly to keep my concentration with such a noise going on.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"any","c":"that","d":"untapped","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- any-> some","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"She presented reward for the return of her lost bracelet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"enrichs","b":"knowledge","c":"listening","d":"every night","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Enrichs-> enriches","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"There is a chill striking me when I go alone in night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"for","c":"books","d":"to which","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To which-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"This morning, I encountered a friend I haven't seen for a long times.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"years","c":"for","d":"last","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- For-> since","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"It is possible to infer two completely opposite conclusion from this set of facts.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Reforming","b":"system","c":"will","d":"difficulty","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Difficulty-> difficult","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}